var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "أُوتِيَ",
        "answer": "is given",
        "pcklId": "523",
        "tlit": "ūtiya",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتِيَ",
        "answer": "is given",
        "pcklId": "524",
        "tlit": "ūtiya",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتَ",
        "answer": "I had been given",
        "pcklId": "525",
        "tlit": "ūta",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدٍ",
        "answer": "one",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "aḥadin",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَخَذَهُمْ",
        "answer": "so He seized them",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "fa-akhadhahum",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "خُذُوهُ",
        "answer": "Seize him",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "khudhūhu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَأَخَذْنَا",
        "answer": "Certainly We (would) have seized",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "la-akhadhnā",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخْذَةً",
        "answer": "(with) a seizure",
        "pcklId": "264",
        "tlit": "akhdhatan",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "Then when",
        "pcklId": "337",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُذُنٌ",
        "answer": "an ear",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "udhunun",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضُ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "439",
        "tlit": "l-arḍu",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُؤْتَفِكَاتُ",
        "answer": "and the overturned cities",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "wal-mu'tafikātu",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلُوا",
        "answer": "Eat",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "kulū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْكُلُهُ",
        "answer": "will eat it",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "yakuluhu",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "536",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "537",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "2791",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "So as for",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "fa-ammā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "And as for",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "wa-ammā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "Then as for",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "fa-ammā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "But as for",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "wa-ammā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُ",
        "answer": "believing",
        "pcklId": "539",
        "tlit": "yu'minu",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "you believe",
        "pcklId": "540",
        "tlit": "tu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُبْصِرُونَ",
        "answer": "you see",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "tub'ṣirūna",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُبْصِرُونَ",
        "answer": "you see",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "tub'ṣirūna",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضَ",
        "answer": "some",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "baʿḍa",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَاقِيَةٍ",
        "answer": "remains",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "bāqiyatin",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَمَانِيَةٌ",
        "answer": "eight",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "thamāniyatun",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَثَمَانِيَةَ",
        "answer": "and eight",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wathamāniyata",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْجِبَالُ",
        "answer": "and the mountains",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "wal-jibālu",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَحِيمَ",
        "answer": "(into) the Hellfire",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "l-jaḥīma",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَارِيَةِ",
        "answer": "the sailing (ship)",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "l-jāriyati",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِنَجْعَلَهَا",
        "answer": "That We might make it",
        "pcklId": "314",
        "tlit": "linajʿalahā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّةٍ",
        "answer": "a Garden",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "jannatin",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَاءَ",
        "answer": "And came",
        "pcklId": "268",
        "tlit": "wajāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَاجِزِينَ",
        "answer": "(who could) prevent (it)",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ḥājizīna",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِسَابِيَهْ",
        "answer": "my account",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "ḥisābiyah",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِسَابِيَهْ",
        "answer": "(is) my account",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "ḥisābiyah",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَحَسْرَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) surely a regret",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "laḥasratun",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُسُومًا",
        "answer": "(in) succession",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ḥusūman",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحُضُّ",
        "answer": "feel the urge",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaḥuḍḍu",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَحَقُّ",
        "answer": "surely (the) truth",
        "pcklId": "274",
        "tlit": "laḥaqqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَاقَّةُ",
        "answer": "The Inevitable Reality",
        "pcklId": "284",
        "tlit": "al-ḥāqatu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَاقَّةُ",
        "answer": "(is) the Inevitable Reality",
        "pcklId": "285",
        "tlit": "l-ḥāqatu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَاقَّةُ",
        "answer": "(is) the Inevitable Reality",
        "pcklId": "286",
        "tlit": "l-ḥāqatu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَمَلْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "We carried you",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "ḥamalnākum",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحُمِلَتِ",
        "answer": "And are lifted",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "waḥumilati",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَحْمِلُ",
        "answer": "and will bear",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "wayaḥmilu",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَمِيمٌ",
        "answer": "any devoted friend",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ḥamīmun",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْخَاطِئَةِ",
        "answer": "with sin",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "bil-khāṭi-ati",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَاطِئُونَ",
        "answer": "the sinners",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-khāṭiūna",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخْفَىٰ",
        "answer": "will be hidden",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "takhfā",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَافِيَةٌ",
        "answer": "any secret",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "khāfiyatun",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَالِيَةِ",
        "answer": "past",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "l-khāliyati",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَاوِيَةٍ",
        "answer": "hollow",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "khāwiyatin",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَدْرِ",
        "answer": "I had known",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "adri",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَدْرَاكَ",
        "answer": "will make you know",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "adrāka",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَدُكَّتَا",
        "answer": "and crushed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fadukkatā",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَكَّةً",
        "answer": "(with) a crushing",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "dakkatan",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَانِيَةٌ",
        "answer": "hanging near",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "dāniyatun",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِرَاعًا",
        "answer": "cubits",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "dhirāʿan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَرْعُهَا",
        "answer": "its length",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "dharʿuhā",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَذَكَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "you take heed",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "tadhakkarūna",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَذْكِرَةً",
        "answer": "a reminder",
        "pcklId": "278",
        "tlit": "tadhkiratan",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَتَذْكِرَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) surely a reminder",
        "pcklId": "279",
        "tlit": "latadhkiratun",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَرَى",
        "answer": "so you would see",
        "pcklId": "242",
        "tlit": "fatarā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "you see",
        "pcklId": "243",
        "tlit": "tarā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "(of) their Lord",
        "pcklId": "892",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "(of) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "893",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "(the) Lord",
        "pcklId": "894",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "(of) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "895",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَابِيَةً",
        "answer": "exceeding",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "rābiyatan",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْجَائِهَا",
        "answer": "its edges",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "arjāihā",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولَ",
        "answer": "(the) Messenger",
        "pcklId": "461",
        "tlit": "rasūla",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولٍ",
        "answer": "(of) a Messenger",
        "pcklId": "462",
        "tlit": "rasūlin",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَاضِيَةٍ",
        "answer": "pleasant",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "rāḍiyatin",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرِيحٍ",
        "answer": "by a wind",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "birīḥin",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَبِّحْ",
        "answer": "So glorify",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "fasabbiḥ",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبْعُونَ",
        "answer": "(is) seventy",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "sabʿūna",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبْعَ",
        "answer": "(for) seven",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "sabʿa",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَخَّرَهَا",
        "answer": "Which He imposed",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "sakharahā",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمِسْكِينِ",
        "answer": "(of) the poor",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "l-mis'kīni",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِلْسِلَةٍ",
        "answer": "a chain",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "sil'silatin",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُلْطَانِيَهْ",
        "answer": "my authority",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "sul'ṭāniyah",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسْلَفْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you sent before you",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "aslaftum",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْلُكُوهُ",
        "answer": "insert him",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "fa-us'lukūhu",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاسْمِ",
        "answer": "(the) name",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "bi-is'mi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءُ",
        "answer": "the heaven",
        "pcklId": "338",
        "tlit": "l-samāu",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاشْرَبُوا",
        "answer": "and drink",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "wa-ish'rabū",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاعِرٍ",
        "answer": "(of) a poet",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "shāʿirin",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَانْشَقَّتِ",
        "answer": "And will split",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wa-inshaqqati",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِشِمَالِهِ",
        "answer": "in his left hand",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "bishimālihi",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَرْصَرٍ",
        "answer": "screaming",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ṣarṣarin",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَرْعَىٰ",
        "answer": "fallen",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ṣarʿā",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَلُّوهُ",
        "answer": "burn him",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ṣallūhu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصُّورِ",
        "answer": "the trumpet ",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "l-ṣūri",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَعَامِ",
        "answer": "(the) feeding",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "ṭaʿāmi",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَعَامٌ",
        "answer": "any food",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "ṭaʿāmun",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَغَى",
        "answer": "overflowed",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ṭaghā",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالطَّاغِيَةِ",
        "answer": "by the overpowering (blast)",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "bil-ṭāghiyati",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَنَنْتُ",
        "answer": "was certain",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "ẓanantu",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَاتِيَةٍ",
        "answer": "violent",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ʿātiyatin",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْجَازُ",
        "answer": "trunks",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "aʿjāzu",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَرْشَ",
        "answer": "(the) Throne",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "ʿarsha",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُعْرَضُونَ",
        "answer": "you will be exhibited",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "tuʿ'raḍūna",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَصَوْا",
        "answer": "And they disobeyed",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "faʿaṣaw",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَظِيمِ",
        "answer": "the Most Great",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "l-ʿaẓīmi",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَظِيمِ",
        "answer": "the Most Great",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "l-ʿaẓīmi",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَنَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "surely know",
        "pcklId": "361",
        "tlit": "lanaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the worlds",
        "pcklId": "545",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَالِيَةٍ",
        "answer": "elevated",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "ʿāliyatin",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَادٌ",
        "answer": "and Aad",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "waʿādun",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَادٌ",
        "answer": "Aad",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "ʿādun",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِيشَةٍ",
        "answer": "a life",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ʿīshatin",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "غِسْلِينٍ",
        "answer": "(the) discharge of wounds",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ghis'līnin",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَغُلُّوهُ",
        "answer": "and shackle him",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "faghullūhu",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَغْنَىٰ",
        "answer": "has availed",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "aghnā",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوْقَهُمْ",
        "answer": "above them",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "fawqahum",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلَهُ",
        "answer": "before him",
        "pcklId": "274",
        "tlit": "qablahu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "اقْرَءُوا",
        "answer": "read",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "iq'raū",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْقَارِعَةِ",
        "answer": "the Striking Calamity",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "bil-qāriʿati",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُقْسِمُ",
        "answer": "I swear",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "uq'simu",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَاضِيَةَ",
        "answer": "the end",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "l-qāḍiyata",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَقَطَعْنَا",
        "answer": "certainly We (would) have cut off",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "laqaṭaʿnā",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُطُوفُهَا",
        "answer": "Its clusters of fruits",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "quṭūfuhā",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "little",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "little",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَقُولُ",
        "answer": "will say",
        "pcklId": "1576",
        "tlit": "fayaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَقُولُ",
        "answer": "will say",
        "pcklId": "1577",
        "tlit": "fayaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقَوَّلَ",
        "answer": "he (had) fabricated",
        "pcklId": "1619",
        "tlit": "taqawwala",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَقَاوِيلِ",
        "answer": "sayings",
        "pcklId": "1620",
        "tlit": "l-aqāwīli",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَقَوْلُ",
        "answer": "surely (the) Word",
        "pcklId": "1709",
        "tlit": "laqawlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِقَوْلِ",
        "answer": "(is the) word",
        "pcklId": "1710",
        "tlit": "biqawli",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِقَوْلِ",
        "answer": "(it is the) word",
        "pcklId": "1711",
        "tlit": "biqawli",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمَ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "483",
        "tlit": "l-qawma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابَهُ",
        "answer": "his record",
        "pcklId": "294",
        "tlit": "kitābahu",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابِيَهْ",
        "answer": "my record",
        "pcklId": "295",
        "tlit": "kitābiyah",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابَهُ",
        "answer": "his record",
        "pcklId": "296",
        "tlit": "kitābahu",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابِيَهْ",
        "answer": "my record",
        "pcklId": "297",
        "tlit": "kitābiyah",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبَتْ",
        "answer": "Denied",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "kadhabat",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُكَذِّبِينَ",
        "answer": "(are) deniers",
        "pcklId": "269",
        "tlit": "mukadhibīna",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَرِيمٍ",
        "answer": "noble",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "karīmin",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "506",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَاهِنٍ",
        "answer": "(of) a soothsayer",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "kāhinin",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَتِ",
        "answer": "had been",
        "pcklId": "1303",
        "tlit": "kānati",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "1304",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُلَاقٍ",
        "answer": "(will) meet",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "mulāqin",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلَيْسَ",
        "answer": "So not",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "falaysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيَالٍ",
        "answer": "nights",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "layālin",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَلَكُ",
        "answer": "And the Angels",
        "pcklId": "191",
        "tlit": "wal-malaku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَالِيَهْ",
        "answer": "my wealth",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "māliyah",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَاءُ",
        "answer": "the water",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "l-māu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَخْلٍ",
        "answer": "(of) date-palms",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "nakhlin",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْزِيلٌ",
        "answer": "(It is) a revelation",
        "pcklId": "282",
        "tlit": "tanzīlun",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُفِخَ",
        "answer": "is blown",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "nufikha",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْخَةٌ",
        "answer": "a blast",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "nafkhatun",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَلَكَ",
        "answer": "Is gone",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "halaka",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأُهْلِكُوا",
        "answer": "they were destroyed",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "fa-uh'likū",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأُهْلِكُوا",
        "answer": "they were destroyed",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "fa-uh'likū",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَنِيئًا",
        "answer": "(in) satisfaction",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "hanīan",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوَتِينَ",
        "answer": "the aorta",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-watīna",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدَةٌ",
        "answer": "single",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "wāḥidatun",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدَةً",
        "answer": "single",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "wāḥidatan",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَعِيَهَا",
        "answer": "and would be conscious of it",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wataʿiyahā",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاعِيَةٌ",
        "answer": "conscious",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wāʿiyatun",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَعَتِ",
        "answer": "will occur",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "waqaʿati",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوَاقِعَةُ",
        "answer": "the Occurrence",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-wāqiʿatu",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُتَّقِينَ",
        "answer": "for the Allah-fearing",
        "pcklId": "255",
        "tlit": "lil'muttaqīna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاهِيَةٌ",
        "answer": "frail",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wāhiyatun",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَقِينِ",
        "answer": "(of) certainty",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "l-yaqīni",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِيَمِينِهِ",
        "answer": "in his right hand",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "biyamīnihi",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْيَمِينِ",
        "answer": "by the right hand",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "bil-yamīni",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيَّامٍ",
        "answer": "days",
        "pcklId": "294",
        "tlit": "ayyāmin",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَيَّامِ",
        "answer": "the days",
        "pcklId": "295",
        "tlit": "l-ayāmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "today",
        "pcklId": "391",
        "tlit": "l-yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "69",
        "ayah": "35"
    }
]; 
export default words;